<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android">
    <string name="app_name">The Bro Code</string>
    <string name="article1">Article 1</string>
    <string name="article2">Article 2</string>
    <string name="article3">Article 3</string>
    <string name="article4">Article 4</string>
    <string name="article5">Article 5</string>
    <string name="article6">Article 6</string>
    <string name="article7">Article 7</string>
    <string name="article8">Article 8</string>
    <string name="article9">Article 9</string>
    <string name="article10">Article 10</string>
    <string name="article11">Article 11</string>
    <string name="article12">Article 12</string>
    <string name="article13">Article 13</string>
    <string name="article14">Article 14</string>
    <string name="article15">Article 15</string>
    <string name="article16">Article 16</string>
    <string name="article17">Article 17</string>
    <string name="article18">Article 18</string>
    <string name="article19">Article 19</string>
    <string name="article20">Article 20</string>
    <string name="article21">Article 21</string>
    <string name="article22">Article 22</string>
    <string name="article23">Article 23</string>
    <string name="article24">Article 24</string>
    <string name="article25">Article 25</string>
    <string name="article26">Article 26</string>
    <string name="article27">Article 27</string>
    <string name="article28">Article 28</string>
    <string name="article29">Article 29</string>
    <string name="article30">Article 30</string>
    <string name="body1">The bond between two men is stronger than the bond between a man and a woman because, on average, men are stronger than women. Thats just science.</string>
    <string name="body2">A bro is always entitled to do something stupid, as long as the rest of his Bros are all doing it</string>
    <string name="body3">If a Bro gets a dog, it must be at least as tall as his knee when full-grown</string>
    <string name="body4">A Bro never divulges the existance of The Bro Code to a woman. It is a sacred doucment not to be shared with chicks for any reason... no, not even that reason</string>
    <string name="body5">Whether he cares about sports or not, a Bro cares about sports.</string>
    <string name="body6">A Bro shall not lollygag if he must get naked in front of other Bros in a gym locker room</string>
    <string name="body7">A Bro never admits he cant drive, even after an accident.</string>
    <string name="body8">A Bro never sends a greeting card to another Bro</string>
    <string name="body9">Should a Bro lose a body part due to an accident or illness, his fellow Bros will not make lame jokes such as Gimme three! or Wowm quitting your job like that really took a lot of ball. Its still a high five and that Bro still has a lot of balls... metaphorically speaking, of course</string>
    <string name="body10">A Bro will drop whatever hes doing and rush to help his Bro dump a chick.</string>
    <string name="body11">A Bro may ask his Bro(s) to help him move, but only after first disclosing an honest estimate on both time commitment and number of large pieces of furniture. If the Bro has vastly underestimated either, his Bros retain the right to leave his possessions where they are - in most cases, stuck in the doorway.</string>
    <string name="body12">Bros do not share dessert.</string>
    <string name="body13">All Bros shall dub one of their bros his wingman</string>
    <string name="body14">If a chick inquires about another Bros sexual history, a Bro shall honour the Brode of Silence and play dumb. Better to have women think all men are stupid than to tell the truth.</string>
    <string name="body15">A Bro never dances with his arms above his head.</string>
    <string name="body16">A Bro never dances with his arms above his head.</string>
    <string name="body17">A Bro shall be kind and courteous to his co-workers, unless they are beneath him on the pyramid of Screaming.</string>
    <string name="body18">If a Bro spearheads a beer run at a party, he is entitled to any excess monies accrued after can canvassing the group.</string>
    <string name="body19">A Bro shall not sleep with another Bro’s sister. However, a Bro shall not get angry of another Bro says, “Dude, your sister’s hot!”</string>
    <string name="body20">A Bro respects all his Bros in the military because they’ve selflessly chose to defend the nation, but more to the point, because they can kick his ass six ways to Sunday.</string>
    <string name="body21">A Bro never shares observations about another Bro’s smoking-hot girlfriend. Even if the Bro with the hot girlfriend attempts to bait the Bro by saying, “She’s smoking-hot, huh?” a Bro shall remain silent, because in this situation, he’s the only one who should be baiting.</string>
    <string name="body22">There is no law that prohibits a woman from being a Bro.</string>
    <string name="body23">When flipping through TV channels with his Bros, a Bro is not allowed to skip past a program featuring boobs. This includes, but is not limited to, exercise shows, women’s athletics, and on some occasions, surgery programs.</string>
    <string name="body24">When wearing a baseball cap, a Bro may position the brim at either 12 or 6 o’ clock. All other angles are reserved for rappers and the handicapped.</string>
    <string name="body25">A Bro doesn’t let another Bro get a tattoo, particularly a tattoo of a girl’s name. – The average relationship between a man and a woman lasts eighty-three days. The relationship between a man and his skin lasts a lifetime and must be nurtured, because as we all know, the skin is the largest and second most important organ a man has.</string>
    <string name="body26">Unless he has children, a Bro shall not wear his cell phone on his belt clip.</string>
    <string name="body27">A Bro never removes his shirt in front of other Bros, unless at a resort pool or the beach.</string>
    <string name="body28">A Bro will, in a temely manner, alert his Bro to the existance of a girl fight. – A Bro must, in a timely manner, communicate the possibility of fisticoffs between two humans of the female variety (Henceforth “girl fight”), in an effot to make possibleand probable that another Bro or Bros can partake in observation. A “timely manner” is open to interpretation based on the initial Bro’s viewing and processing of the potential feminine conflagration. Said Bro must use any and all methods of media distribution at his disposal, including but not limited to: telecommunications, elbow nudging, carrier piggions, fiber optics, shouting, postcards, and telepathy. If an informed Bro is unable to witness the girl fight firsthand, the spotter Bro is responsible for documenting and relating details of the girl fight via pictures, video, or, barring any other reasonable method, interpretive dance and/or pantomime</string>
    <string name="body29">If two Bros decide to catch a movie together, they may not attend a screening that begins after 4:40 PM. Also, despite the cost savings, they shall not split a tub of popcorn, choosing instead to procure individual bags.</string>
    <string name="body30">A Bro doesn’t comparison shop</string>
    <string name="Body31">When on the prowl, a Bro hits on the hottest chick first because you just never know.</string>
    <string name="Body32">A Bro doesn\'t allow another Bro to get married until he\'s at least thirty.</string>
    <string name="body33">When in a public restroom, a Bro (1) stares straight ahead when using the urinal; (2) makes the obligatory comment, &quot;What is this, a chicks' restroom?&quot; if there are more than two dudes waiting to pee; and (3) attempts to basketball toss his used paper towel into the trash can like a basketball...rebounding is optional.</string>
    <string name="body34">Bros cannot make eye-contact during a Devil\'s Three-way. </string>
    <string name="body35">A Bro never rents a chick flick.</string>
    <string name="body36">When questioned in the company of women, a Bro always decries fake breasts.</string>
    <string name="body37">A Bro is under no obligation to open a door for anyone. If women insist on having their own professional basketball league, then they can open their own doors. Honestly they\'re not that heavy. </string>
    <string name="body38">Even in a fight to the death a Bro never punches another Bro in the groin.</string>
    <string name="body39">When a Bro gets a chicks number, he waits at least ninety-six hours before calling her. The reason is Bro-flation. An unreasonable increase in female expectations about how bros should act. You call a woman the next day, she tells her friends that you called the next day, and soon enough, women everywhere will expect guys to call them the next day. Before you know it, bros the world over will find themselves trapped in relationships and all because you couldn’t wait 96 little hours.</string>
    <string name="body40">Should a Bro become stricken with engagement, his Bros shall stage an intervention and attempt to heal him. This is more commonly known as a bachelor party.</string>
    <string name="body41">A Bro never cries. Exceptions- Watching Field of Dreams, ET or a sports legend retire (only first time he retires).</string>
    <string name="body42">Upon greeting another Bro, a Bro may engage in a high five, fist bump, or a Bro hug, but never a full embrace.</string>
    <string name="body43"> A Bro loves his country, unless that country isn\'t America.</string>
    <string name="body44">A Bro never applies sunscreen to another Bro. Exceptions – If the Bros are within 7 degrees latitude of the equator.</string>
    <string name="body45">A Bro never wears jeans to a strip club. Reasons – a) Cloth pockets are roomier and elastic allowing for a thicker wad of cash. b) Denim clashes with the club’s leopard, zebra or other safari animal motif. c) One word, two syllables, three hours in the ER – Zipper. d) It’s a performance and deserves respect. e) You don’t feel it as much on your… you know what.. </string>
    <string name="body46">If a Bro is seated next to some dude who\'s stuck in the middle seat on an airplane, he shall yield him all of their shared armrest, unless the dude has A. taken his shoes off, B. is snoring, C. makes the Bro get up more than once to use the lavatory, or D. purchased headphones after they announced the in-flight movie is 27 Dresses. See Article 35.</string>
    <string name="body47">A Bro never wears pink. Not even in Europe.</string>
    <string name="body48">A Bro never publicly reveals how many chicks he\'s banged. Corollary – A bro also never reveals how many chicks another Bro has banged. </string>
    <string name="body49"> When asked, Do you need some help? a Bro shall automatically respond, I got it, whether or not he\'s actually got it. Exceptions Carrying an expensive TV, parallel parking an expensive car and loading an expensive TV on to an expensive car.</string>
 
       
   
   </resources>